Awe, I'm out of lighter fluid.
It's too much of a hassle to go buy
more, and the gas is shut off right now.
If I put this one out,
I can't smoke anymore.
Wow, I'm a genius.
I think I'm just going to
keep smoking till the morning.
Oh
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
I'll clean all this up, okay?
Oh, are you done eating?
Wait a minute, Hame.
Excuse me!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hakai-san, Dasai, and Koshin no Kanbei!
Three sake cups here?
Those are all mine.
Hey!
There are three cups,
so it's for everyone.
Ooh, okay, Crum.
Straight out of the bottle?
I need you.
Oh, just go left and
turn right at the end.
Thank you.
Wow, that was one heck of a fall.
You, uh?
Order's ready.
Hey, Kamei, remember when you
wet yourself in that last dream?
What the hell?
I didn't wet myself during the last
dream What are you talking about?
Where's the bathroom?
I was supposed to turn right somewhere
Where?
That's the end.
Where is it?
Thank you very much!
Where am I? Hang on.
So where are you headed?
To Aoshima?
I don't know.
Oh, there she is.
What's she doing?
So, anyway, the sunrise was beautiful.
We were just choking, right?
There's no way she went to Inoshima.
I don't know where y 'all took that
picture, but that's a good one.
Can I turn up the AC?
Yeah, sure.
Good call.
This humidity's got the air
feeling thicker than gravy today.
It's got my hair all frizzed
up, and I can't stand it.
Speaking of hair, Aruko,
you should cut yours soon.
What are you, a Higa Madon
that just landed in Omori?
Cause Higa Madon get puffy?
So I thought it was funny!
I'm just waiting for all
the laughter to die down.
You sure know how to crush
a girl's spirit, don't you?
It was way puffier when
it landed in Amuri.
Thanks for clearing that up!
Wait a second?
Haven't you made that joke before?
What are you?
Some kind of Higa Madon at the beach?
It wasn't even funny the first time you
said it I apologize, oh, big-haired one.
It would be honored to cut said hair.
While I do that, can you not
point out how bad my joke was?
Hold on.
Oh.
My.
Cartridge.
You knew that was in there?
Yeah, and the bigger her hair gets, the
more stuff I can store inside of it.
That's nice.
What's wrong with you?
Her hair ain't your cabinet.
Well, if you lost things as much as I
do, you'd store stuff in big hair, too.
Don't be afraid of test
driving it yourself.
Hang on a second.
You're okay with her using your
head like a storage unit, Auro?
It doesn't bother me.
Stand up for yourself, you knucklehead.
Goodness gracious.
Oh, uh, did you leave any
room in here for her head?
Pretty sure I'm seeing at least five
beast folk rats violations here.
Huh?
Oh, those are mine.
It's not always easy to find a place
to store some needles, you know.
Uh, see.
Well, here you go, then.
Thanks.
Uh, was I just smoking a ghost cigarette?
You sure you didn't finish it?
A burning cigarette in a run-down
apartment wasn't on my bingo card today.
Do you guys smell something burning?
Those flames got big real quick.
Pretty dang impressive right there.
She's just sitting there burning alive.
She ain't hot.
That ghost cigarette must be made of 10
cigarettes to get a flame this big going.
This is nuts!
I get it now!
All that booze she keeps putting
away must have seeped into her hair.
One little spark and now
she's a ball of fire.
Data collected.
Theory confirmed.
How the hell is she not freaking out?
Hang tight just for a sec.
Seriously? Okey dokey.
That's messed up.
This is your fault, you fucking kiddies!
All right, bye-bye to all the burnt parts.
Change smoker cut!
The truth is, I haven't really
been feeling that creative lately.
You haven't, huh?
The problem is that I get
all of these little pieces
of different stories constantly
popping into my head,
but then as soon as I think
I can piece them together,
they disappear.
Oh, well that's actually
pretty common, I hear.
It happens to you too?
There's just never enough
time in the day, right?
Your work isn't recognized
until it's out in the world,
but before I can give form to my ideas,
the endless stream of delusions, my
loneliness brings tears into pieces!
Then before I know it, the day's
over and I haven't done anything!
That sounds rough.
Can I check your screen
time real quick? What?
Uh, let me look at your phone.
Yeah, okay.
Hmm. Yikes.
She's on that for about 60 hours a week.
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh!
Chainsoga Cat! Oh!
Good evening.
You're listening to the Aluminium Bat Duo.
We've got another hot summer.
Yeah, something I'm noticing,
I still see people going outside
for a smoke in this heat.
Doesn't matter how much they sweat.
How much longer till
we get to where Aru is?
Uh, it's about 20 minutes away.
Why'd you go from Nyagamihara to Inoshima?
Right?
Yeah, but still, smoking is nasty.
Okay, picture this.
You're in bed with a woman, right?
You're out of breath.
Here we go.
And then you dig into
some Japanese barbecue.
Oh, yeah.
You visit your parents during Obon?
Huh?
Uh, no, I didn't.
I didn't feel up to it.
They'd be happy if you visited.
They're good people.
You think so?
Yeah, of course.
What can I say?
I'm a simple man, right.
And you know what?
Uh, cool if I smoke?
Huh? Sure.
Use the ashtray, though. Okay.
All gorillas have type B blood.
Oh, really?
So, the other day, I...
Oh, also, you can go first.
No, it's okay.
It was nothing important.
You go ahead.
No, no, no.
All right, folks, it's time.
To say goodbye for the day
this show was brought to
you by the Yamaplex Beast
Articles Production Committee.
I hope you all have a wonderful
evening. Bye, guys. Bye.
It's so beautiful.
Nice.
I finally managed to draw a straight line.
I'm really sorry about this, Tataro.
Your usual assistants weren't
available, unfortunately.
Oh, that's perfect.
I know. I know. Oh, hold on.
I went ahead and reached
out to a temp agency
and found a few experienced
assistants for you.
Just make sure to meet
that deadline, okay?
I have no choice.
I have to hit this huge deadline.
I have to roll with it.
Everyone decided to
visit family this week.
These new people better be really good.
Hello, we're here from the
Beesfolk Temp Agency, Beast Pal.
Three strangers in my home.
I'll be fine, right?
I know that most Beast
Folk are usually easygoing.
Hey! Excuse me? Yes!
Oh, are you finished?
Okay, let's see what we've got.
Alright, here we go.
She's still doing Black
Fill on the first panel?
She's been working on it for two hours!
You're filling it in nicely.
I'm seeing some good work here.
She gave me a compliment.
You're lucky.
She's really nice.
Well, they don't seem like bad kids to me.
Is there anybody here who
doesn't smoke or... Me?
Of course you don't.
Hi.
Excuse me.
She's in charge of screen tones.
She's definitely faster than
the girls doing black fill.
It's a little messy, though.
It's great.
Keep up the good work.
She's been carving out
the middle of the sheet?
What is she trying to do?
Cut clean through the desk?
I won't say anything.
I just need to get through
this shitty deadline.
Oh, one thing.
For the background, I wanted
to add another window.
How's it going so far?
Sure.
There.
Great thank you it's fine
it's fine my drawings are
already weird enough that
I can get away with this
but I have to finish the
manuscript if no matter
what deadlines can't change
I'm going to get this done
How many hours has it been since I last
slept my vision is getting blurry and I?
have a headache.
What am I even trying to do?
What the hell is all of this?
It's not even art.
I'm
just making stains on the paper.
The third panel is done!
Oh, now you're gonna go have her look at
it again, aren't ya?
Nobody likes a cheater! Excuse me.
The buck fells.
She's only done two
more panels.
Listen, you have to stop coming
to me for every single panel.
At least wait until
you've finished a whole page, will you?
This is just a waste of time.
And from now on, while you're all working?
Could you be a bit quieter?
What am i what am i
even doing hey you guys
i'm sorry for the way
i treated you earlier.
I was frustrated because my back was
against the wall and i took it out on you
i'll never get angry again please don't
leave i can't do this without you all?
Let's get this done!
Really great work!
Thank you so much for staying extra!
The temp agency is going to get an
A rating about you guys from me!
I hope we get to do this together again.
Okay!
Only three pages left just the inking then
i'm done two hours until the deadline.
They say you can only use your
abilities cage five times in your life
for me one of those times
is right now let's go!
She was such a nice person
wasn't she yeah let's
work on our skills so we can
be more useful next time!
Smoking i love it!
I'm here to pick up the manuscript!
Why are you always boiling
grass, Pen-Pen-Neko?
You broke or what?
Hmm.
You mustn't let yourself
be bound by social values.
When you abandon it all and choose
to live in harmony with nature,
only then will you see the truth.
Yeah, but you still have
a tent and other stuff.
I found all of this, so there is no harm.
Hi, kitty cat.
It claimed this area as its territory.
Although it may be small, this
cat is more experienced than I am.
Feeling the wind, making
the earth your home.
This one's a seeker of life's meaning.
As such, this cat is worthy
of the utmost response.
It just bit you.
Yes, well, every feeling has a purpose.
Even pain has something
important to teach us
all that's some healthy
blood flow right there
It is nothing the gentle
wind will heal me.
Yeah
Well, no cigarettes means it's
time to go home. Farewell.
You need no invitation to return
This really hurts that get a tiny
swords for teeth For sure it's infected.
You seen a lighter around?
What's wrong?
Your lighter is over there.
Are your turning around muscles broken?
They're fine.
Don't be a weirdo. Look at me.
I cannot.
Please don't worry.
This is nothing.
When you choose to become one with nature,
your tears will...
Oh, a half-use cigarette.
All right, see you later.
We're staring at a
once-in-a-century downpour.
Relentless rain.
Tents of drowning in the streets.
This is exciting.
I want to go out and catch a frog.
The sweet, seductive scent of
committing a dangerous act.
Your feelings are understandable,
but you must resist.
Nyanineko, hunger has always been the driving
force of humanity since its inception.
The hunger grew to material things,
carnal pleasures, power, the list goes on.
All these desires share a common thread.
They have inspired great
conflict in our world.
I choose to live the
way I do because I want
to prove that we have the
ability to resist even
our most tempting yearnings
look when you continue
to live a life without
desire nothing will be
able to shake your resolve
my hope is that you
also learn to let go of
your attachments there will
always be frogs waiting
I didn't want to catch
them because I wanted to
eat them yeah these angry
waters are sweeping away
anything in its path
oh that poor man he craves
material things so he
subjects himself to this
work huh nyagami river
hey that's where you live
oh a large piece of trash
is floating down the river
down and goes now it's
time for our next segment
cancer today back to
the studio holy that's
my tent get away from
there it's dangerous Can
I get some help over here?
What are you saying?
Chainsmoker Cat.
All right, let's go.
Well, summer, it's been fun.
Oh
Thank you.